Today is the day.
Hm? For what?
You have to ask?
It's the day Eden College announces
the admissions results.
The results should be posted
at 1200 hours today.
This is more nerve-racking
than I thought it'd be.
My bracelet just broke.
Why did it have to happen today?
Oh, I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
L-Loid, look.
Oh, come on, Yor. Black cats being
unlucky is just a superstition.
Y-You're right.
Papa...
What's the matter?
I just stepped in poop.
Admissions results for Eden College?
Ah, the thing we've got Agent Twilight doing.
Chief, peace between the East
and West hangs on Operation Strix.
Please take this more seriously.
You don't know Twilight very well, do you?
C-Correct, sir.
Underwear:
He might just be the best spy in all
of Westalis, so don't worry so much.
He'll be telling us that "the sakura
blossoms bloom" soon enough.
What does that mean, sir?
It's a code phrase from the Far East.
It means they passed.
It's not there.
WILL THEY PASS OR FAIL?
We failed...
We failed.
L-Let's head home.
I-I'll make us some tea.
I'm sorry... It's all because I stepped in poop.
A moment, Forgers.
Master Henderson...
What is this?
Look at the very top.
Anya Forger...
That is the waiting list of successful
applicants, though rather confidential.
A waiting list?
Correct. Once her overall scores were tallied,
Anya Forger placed first on that waiting list.
If any of the current successful
applicants were to withdraw,
she'll immediately get into the school.
B-But after what we did...
Do you know what the number one killer
of our species on this planet is?
Huh?
It is the mosquito!
Yes. You saved Master Swan from
that brutal killer back there.
That brought your score up tremendously.
That's insane.
Stand proud, Forger.
Your family is worthy of our school.
So if even one person withdraws,
Miss Anya will get in?
Correct.
But if no one withdraws...
Now, about that...
Th-The Thorn Princess?
What are you doing here?
Secretary Zachry Feiss, I presume?
If it's not too much trouble,
I will be taking your life.
Please, no! Spare me!
I have a son who's just about to turn six!
He'll be starting at Eden College next month!
If I die, he won't be able to go to school!
I'm terribly sorry, but that's
exactly why I'm doing this.
Huh?!
For the sake of Miss Anya
getting into the school...
I need you to die!
You mustn't, Yor!
You mustn't take the life
of an innocent person, Yor!
Yor?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Zachry Feiss.
Well, no matter.
There are a few that withdraw every year.
Make sure you are properly
prepared for the eventuality.
Thank you very much, Master Henderson.
I must warn you that I may not be
teaching here by the time you arrive.
What?
I was forced to give that
swine a good thrashing.
I was able to protect Eden's honor,
but who know what ramifications await me?
That foolish man and this instructor...
I'm not sure which one will be
more useful to me in my mission,
but if that fool stands in my way,
I have plenty of ways to destroy him.
Please let me know if there's
anything I can do to help.
I appreciate the attempt at
consolation, my elegant boy.
Just await that call at home.
Days
Later
Anya will be accepted...
What in the world is she doing?
Apparently, she's performing a prayer
dance to help her get accepted.
Anya will be accepted...
Oh... I see.
Kieeeeeeeh!
Hello, Forger residence.
Yes.
Goodbye.
Anya got in!
Papa! I passed!
You did a great job, Anya!
I did it!
Oh, thank goodness! What wonderful news!
I'm so happy!
Thank you for all you did as well, Yor.
Heya. I heard she got in.
Time to celebrate!
You sure found out fast.
Never underestimate an informant.
Oh, you must be the missus.
Pleasure to meet you!
I'm Loid's friend, Franky!
Hello.
Scruffy-scruff!
Let's get this party started! I got
some booze, and I ordered delivery!
Who do you think you are?
This is all thanks to me
stealing the answer sheet.
You idiot! They'll hear you!
Huh? Wha wuz zat?
Are you even drinking, you party pooper?
Leave me be.
Isn't it great, Anya?
Daddy said he'll buy you anything
as a reward just for today!
Hey! Don't go promising her things like that!
I don't want you to buy me anything,
but I wanna do something!
Hm? What's that?
I don't mind as long as it's doable.
Save me, Bondman!
Good morning, Bondman.
Your mission today is to save
the kidnapped Princess Honey,
and take her back the castle.
Wait for me, Princess Honey!
The kingdom's best spy infiltrates the castle...
Bondman!
Taking down any enemy that stands in his way,
he finally makes it to the princess.
I'm here to save you, Princess Honey!
Bondman!
Peace was restored to the castle,
and their love continued to grow.
This is what I wanna do.
What you wanna do? Wait, you mean...
I wanna play "save Anya from the castle"!
Nope. Not happening.
How cruel... You meanie!
I'm not going to school if you don't do this!
No one asked you to speak for her.
Oh, hey. I'm pretty sure that's Newston Castle.
I heard it was recently remodeled
into some cartoon's theme park,
but that's definitely it.
It's got the same kinds of
tricks and traps seen in the show,
and you can even rent it out.
The government doesn't have any
eyes over there, Loidy Boy,
so it wouldn't hurt to have a little bit of fun.
But...
After everything she went through to pass, too.
Doesn't seem fair if you can't get
some kind of reward, huh, kiddo?
Sniffle, sniffle...
Sniffle, sniffle.
Sniffle...
All right, fine.
Right, then! Let's strike while the iron's hot!
Leave the castle reservation to me.
You're in charge of our ride!
Wha?! You expect us to go today?
And you want me to arrange this?
Well, of course! It's for your daughter!
We have a message from Twilight.
Code GO005.
He did it.
"The sakura blossoms bloom."
Another message from Twilight.
What is it?
How shall I reply?
He might just be the best
spy in all of Westalis...
Get him what he needs at once!
Yes, ma'am!
To Falcon in the Rhynnick region.
Emergency operation from Twilight.
Falcon here. Roger the emergency
operation from Twilight, over.
"1830 hours... Meet downstream on the
Nein River in the Rhynnick region."
They sure didn't waste any time.
Believe it or not, this castle can do this, too!
I'm gonna make a quiz!
Hey, great idea!
You seriously came through!
Anya's never been on a
plane before! It's so exciting!
Nice, nice, nice!
There we go.
Does Anya look cool?
Yes, you do.
Loid! Where did you get this li'l plane?
It's amazing!
Oh, some wonderful coworkers of
mine are letting me borrow it.
Fank you for always looking
after my husband.
You all have your seatbelts on? Here we go.
Let's go!
I'm so excited!
Yahoo!
Oh, it's so pretty.
It looks like a tweasure chest.
Papa, you're amazing!
Look! There it is!
Holy crap!
The castle's so cool!
Hey, settle down!
We're about to land.
Make sure you're properly seated.
We're in a castle!
You don't need to go running around with her!
This is wonderful.
What's the matter?
Something's not right.
What do you mean by that?
Can you truly call a castle
with no enemies or servants
a castle?
I'm sad.
I don't think I can go to school now.
I know, right? I can't blame ya, little missy.
Daddy better step up his game.
We have a report from Twilight.
He's requesting agents.
As many as possible.
This will be a true test for WISE.
To all agents in Ostania.
Report to Newston Castle
for an emergency operation.
This is an extremely important
assignment regarding Operation Strix.
Mission rank is over SS.
I repeat: this is an extremely important
assignment regarding Operation Strix.
Mission rank is over SS!
That's the real Twilight...
I gotta get his autograph later.
Look at your agency coming through for you.
Well, give them the rundown.
I'll explain the rest.
All right, fine.
Thank you very much for gathering
here today on behalf of my daughter.
Morse code.
"Just listen quietly."
Orders from Twilight!
I would like for all of you to
play the part of the enemies
This assignment is an imperative part of Operation Strix, and you do not to need to inquire further about it
of a spy who is coming to save a princess.
I have absolutely no idea what's going on...
But this is Twilight we're talking about.
I'm sure this is all according to plan.
This man will explain the details. Follow his orders from now on
Thank you again for doing
this for my daughter.
All right! Let's announce the cast!
Here's our star for today!
Princess Anya!
This is the spy person who's gonna save me!
Loidman!
And the big bad boss!
Scruffy!
Count Scruffy Head!
And Mama... um...
can be whatever.
Shock!
And now...
to the very capable subordinates
of Count Scruffy Head!
I need you all to put on
your best performances
and get in Loidman's
way as much as possible!
Uh... wait...
This mission ranking is over SS.
I'll make any sacrifice necessary
to see this mission through!
I couldn't ask for a better
opponent than Twilight!
This day has finally come...
You can all decide for yourselves how
you're going to get in Loidman's way.
I am not exaggerating when I say the
success of this plan is in your hands!
Uh... Where is this going?
My loyal minions!
Make Loidman suffer as much as
possible for Princess Anya's sake!
Once you're all prepared,
get to your positions!
Roger!
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
Princess Anya is mine!
If you want her back, come after me!
Save me, Loidman.
Wait, it's already started?!
Hey!
Loidman! You are about to face many
obstacles in order to get the princess back!
First up,
we have a quiz that the princess made
up in this courtyard, so listen up!
If you can't answer correctly,
you'll be putting that on!
This is...
You betcha! A Bondman costume set!
So exciting!
Okay, question time!
What does Princess Anya like about Bondman?!
Huh? His face?
Bzzz! The fact that he has
a pistol with a silencer!
What? Really?!
Oh, come on! You're her dad
and you don't even know that?
Next question!
What's Anya's favorite food?
Peanuts!
Ooh! Correct!
Tch. Guess that was too easy.
Here's the final question!
If you get it wrong, you'll be
changing into that outfit, Loidman!
That's if I don't get it.
Here's your question, then.
What does Anya want right now?
What does she want right now?
Five! Four!
You didn't say anything about a time limit!
I never said there wouldn't be one, either.
Calm down. What does Anya want right now?
What does she want...
Bondman's spy gear!
What's the correct answer, Princess Anya?!
Right now...
I'm thirsty, so I'd like some water, please!
Looks like you're wrong, Loidman!
How the hell would I know that?!
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
Too bad for you, Loidman!
Now, let's have you keep your word!
I'm so excited...
to see the real Loidman!
Loidman!
All right, then! On to the next stage!
Hey, wait!
Loidman!
If you want to save Princess Anya,
you'll have to make your way up here!
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
He's so cool!
He's just so amazing...
You're so cool, Loidman!
We're just getting started, scruff!
Oh, no. Save me.
God, this is pain.
Loidman! Up here, up here!
I'm right here!
There's no end to this.
This is so cool!
You've got this, my minions!
Don't let him win!
Loid! Let them hit you, damn it!
Now you've done it, you bastard!
Don't think you're gonna catch us that easily!
Buh-bye!
Save me, Loidman.
You're so amazing, Loidman!
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
I'm impressed you got this far, Loidman!
But I won't let you have the princess!
Save me, Loidman!
Are you seriously telling me
I have to act out this embarrassing
little play in front of all of these agents?
But in the end... this is for the mission!
H... Hand over the princess.
Ooh!
I can't believe we get to see
Twilight's acting skills in person!
You fool! You think I'd
hand her over that easily?!
Now, go! The most powerful
witch in the world, Yorticia!
Finish off that fool, scruff!
Now there's a witch?!
What the hell is going on in this story?
Huh?
Wai—no way. What?!
Anyone who tries to kidnap Miss Anya...
will not get away alive!
Y-Yor, please calm down.
Why is she using physical
attacks when she's a witch?
She's strong!
She's gonna kill me!
Yor... Are you all right?
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
Excellent work getting this far, Loidman!
But you won't defeat me that easil—
So exciting!
I... I've come to save you, Princess Anya.
Papa!
Wait... I'm supposed to be your dad in this?
So sparkly!
Congratulations, Anya!
Anya...
Congratulations...
What is this?
I've had so much excitement
ever since I left the orphanage!
It's all thanks to you, Papa!
Hm? Oh... I'm happy for you.
I'm gonna do my best in school!
That's good.
Well, anyway... congratulations
on getting into the school.
Sir, the expense report from Agent Twilight.
Are these numbers real?
Yes, they are.
But...
They are correct.
Mission Report
Operation Strix
Phase 1: School Admission achieved
THE FRIENDSHIP SCHEME